



# **Valery Tolmachev**

Nationality: Latvian Date of birth: 31/03/1996 Gender: Male

Phone number: (+371) 22516636 Email address: valerijstolmacevs@gmail.com

**Facebook:** <a href="https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100033024713422">https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100033024713422</a>

O Home: Kaniera iela 20, LV-1011 Riga (Latvia)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm 26 years old. I learned about coding by making websites using site builders like webflow. at first, it was a hobby. but then I was intrigued to make websites with more difficult logic. and at this point, I began learning to code. I began learning javascript. learned about frontend, backend, and algorithms. then fell in love with this area. I am intrigued to learn new things. explore new technologies and take the part in developing projects that gonna be used by a lot of people

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Javscript / Node js / React / Next js / Figma / Html / Css / Typescript

#### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Russian

#### Other language(s):

**English** Latvian

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B1 LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1 SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

### **PROJECTS**

#### Cooking master classes website

I was doing this project from scratch. design, and developing using site builder Webflow. I was using javascript to extend Webflow features.

Link: https://www.foodanatomy.eu/

#### eCommerce site offering cooking knifes

the aim was to create knife e-commerce project. i was using Webflow site builder. custom code using javascript. Weglot to translate the site into different languages.

password of this website - 67253923Home

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Junior cook

**Double Coffee** [ 01/01/2015 - 01/01/2016 ]

#### Kitchen chef

**Double Coffee** [ 01/01/2016 - 01/01/2017 ]

#### Cook

**Gastronome** [ 01/01/2018 - 01/01/2020 ]

#### **Executive Chef**

**Beer museum** [ 01/01/2020 - 01/01/2021 ]

# Second kitchen chef

**Gastronome** [ 01/01/2021 - 01/01/2023 ]

# **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### **Trainee**

**Double Coffee** [ 01/01/2015 – 01/01/2016 ]

# Trainee

*Vincent* [ 02/01/2017 - 01/01/2018 ]

# **Pastry trainee**

**Gastronome** [ 01/01/2018 – 01/01/2019 ]

# intership in France

**Gastronome** [ 01/01/2022 - 01/01/2023 ]